Watching videos on mobile.
Thank you for coming.
Thank you.
I was surprised.
The content of this video is sudden.
Can you write the name of Miyagi?
Name?
What is the name?
The name of the prefecture.
I only know the name of the prefecture.
I just knew that there is such a thing.
I can't do this.
I have more opportunities to go to
various places.
I thought it would be better to learn
the prefecture's mark verification.
I will give you the paper that has been
verified.
You will be measured and recorded for 3
minutes.
Do you remember?
I will collect the paper in 3 minutes.
After that, you will be measured by
showing only the mark.
Why did you make this a memory?
Sakura took a break from the general
common sense test.
I think there is a general common sense
test.
But no one has to take the test.
So, I will change the direction of the
test.
This is a memory test.
First, I will collect the paper.
I don't want to do this.
Let's eat.
I don't want to eat.
Are you ready?
I can't do this.
What if you don't know the prefecture?
I want to eat a lot.
Are you ready?
I can't do this.
Why?
Let's start.
Are you ready?
Yay!
Wow, this is impossible!
Wait, wait, wait.
It's like an Olympic.
I can't do it.
Is this a team game?
It's a speed game.
Speed game!
Which one do you like?
Definitely, the silver one.
You are noisy.
I don't like it.
I'll collect them.
I can't remember anything.
Me, neither.
The first question.
Oh, I'm serious.
I couldn't answer this.
Did you like it?
Maybe.
You said Kitami.
Please subscribe to our channel.
I love you.
The second question.
Sakura of now.
Okinawa.
You are right.
Hiroshima.
Hiroshima is wrong.
Okinawa is correct.
Great.
Are you smart?
The third question.
The answer is Tachibana.
Yamagata.
I haven't heard the answer for a long
time.
I'm glad.
I'm happy with the answer.
The fourth question.
What is the answer?
The answer is Sakura.
Chiba.
No, it's not.
Kaiko.
I'm glad.
I haven't heard the answer.
The fifth question.
What is the answer?
The answer is Osaka.
I'm scared.
It's amazing.
Why?
I'm scared.
Why did you know the answer?
I don't know.
I remember that I changed my clothes.
I see.
You are wearing a T-shirt with this
T-shirt.
That's right.
I got it.
It's amazing.
The sixth question.
The answer is Nagano.
Why?
I'm scared.
It's similar to the answer in the game.
Is that so?
It's amazing.
Thank you.
Let's get along with each other.
I think I'll get the answer.
I think so, too.
I'm going to get the answer.
The seventh question.
What is the answer?
Kanagawa?
I got it.
I remembered that.
I didn't get anything.
You got everything.
I remember everything.
The eighth question.
Miyagi.
You got it quickly.
Is this Miyagi?
I got it.
Why is this Miyagi?
I don't know.
Did you get it?
I got it.
What did you get?
What are you talking about?
The ninth question.
Iwate.
I wanted to remember Iwate.
I'm not good at this.
Thank you for watching this video.
Please subscribe to this channel.
équipe
What is this?
Are you really saying it?
I understand everything so far.
I'm so scared.
I feel like I'm the end of a human
being.
It's okay.
I'm shaking.
Amazing.
Should I buy a treasure chest?
11 questions.
What is this?
Did you study?
I don't know.
I wanted to answer this.
What is this?
Please answer.
I don't know what it is.
12 questions.
Who is it?
Fukuoka?
No.
I don't know.
I remember it.
I remember it by the name of a roadside
station.
What is it?
Roadside station?
I know it.
What is it?
I don't know.
Don't worry.
I remember it as peach.
What is a girl with a beard?
It's not peach.
Is that so?
The 13th place.
I remember it as this.
I will say it randomly.
Riku
It's a beard.
Kagoshima
Kumamoto
Akita
That was fast.
Hokkaido
And, Togigata
Kyushu?
Do you want me to say it?
Yes
Did you go there with your friends?
Yes, we did.
To be continued?
When did you go to Tochigi?
Eggplant?
Eggplant and Gyoza.
Thank you!
I'm so happy!
The 14th question.
What is the name of the restaurant?
The answer is...
How did you know?
Rock, paper, scissors!
Wait, what was it?
No, no, I have no confidence.
Do your best!
Kuma?
That's amazing.
Why did you remember?
I'm sorry, grandpa.
I was defeated.
Question 15.
Shizuoka!
I didn't know.
It's like Aomori.
What?
Aomori?
I'm not opening it.
How many points did you get?
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10
You have 5 questions left.
But you can't win.
So, you have 2 points.
Wow!
I'm so happy.
The 16th question.
Yes.
Hiroshima.
Wow!
I'm so happy.
17 questions.
Tachibana.
Fudo.
I'm sore, everyone in this park is an
old Gochisama,
really mixture
went
as
It's Kyoto after all.
That's Kyoto.
There's a city.
It's beautiful.
It's cute.
Question 18.
What was it?
This is cute.
Niigata.
Nagano.
Hiroshima.
What was it?
Saitama.
Satori.
Niigata.
I can't give you a hint.
Oh, that's a hint.
What is it?
Takasaki.
Takasaki is Gunma.
Kagoshima.
Ehime
Ibaraki
Nagasaki
Oh!
Nen Nagasaki
L
You might get it right even if you
don't know the answer.
What is it?
Sottori
Correct!
I'm glad I remembered this.
I'm in trouble.
Next, the last one.
What is the score?
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7.
If I get that, I may get 9 points.
That's great.
I'll do my best.
I'm sad.
I can't say anything.
What do you want to get?
Well...
You can't say it.
I want to get the lowest score.
The second question.
Please subscribe to this channel.
Thank you for watching.
It's the third one.
What are you doing?
The third one.
We all have 9 points.
You have to pass the person who you
hit.
I see.
Let's start.
Yamanashi Enkime.
Yamaguchi.
Kogareki.
Aichi.
for
me
Guy and Six Ark
Nine
Lee
Hai
Today
What is this?
A coin!
A triangle?
A collab!
Why?
You should have pushed it!
What is this?
I'm a little bit.
So, the winner is Hitomi.
What?
I thought I was going to win.
So, Hitomi will start from zero points
with two other girls.
Hitomi has more time to remember than
you, so we'll talk about the points as
adults.
I'm a little bit shy.
So, this was the first quiz.
Thank you for watching.
We learned a lot today.
Today's leader is a negative leader.
I'll close the video.
If you enjoyed today's video, please
press like button.
This was Karen, Hina and Hinano.
Bye bye.
Please look forward to the next video.